https://www.manoshomecare.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you visit our site, fill out forms, or view PDF’s .When visiting our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To improve customer serviceTo send periodic emailsThe email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.Information SharingBy providing us with your information, you agree to allow Manos to share your personal information with third parties in ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We may provide your personal information to companies in whose products or services we think you may have interest, based on the information you provide. We may also share your personal information:As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal processWhen we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a government requestIn connection with changes in the business including merger, acquisition or sale of assetsTo any other third party with your prior consentNote: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.Do we use cookies?Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain informationIf you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone.We also use the Google Adwords tracking cookie for remarketing. This means that you may continue to see ads as you visit other websites across the internet. We respect your privacy and are not collecting any information that can be used to identify you through the use of Google’s remarketing system. Google will place cookies on web browsers in order to show ads that are based on your visits to our website. This allows Home Care Pulse to make special offers and market our services to visitors who have shown interest in our service. You can opt out of Google’s Analytics and remarketing here.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below, or send us a note.Welcome! Manos Home Care has been providing in-home services for adults and children with developmental disabilities throughout the East Bay since 1989.Quick LinksHomeAbout UsServicesCase ManagersParentsEmployeesFAQ’sCareersJob DescriptionContact UsPrivacy PolicyContact 4173 MacArthur Blvd
Oakland, CA 94619
510-336-2900
877-301-1707
Monday - Friday8:30 a.m - 12:00 noon,
1:00 p.m - 5:00 p.m© Copyright manoshomecare - All Rights Reserved.
